TREVER OVESON

Springville, UT 84663

Phone: 385-233-8011 | Email: toveson9522@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/trever-oveson | github.com/toveson | https://toveson.github.io/react-portfolio/#/

SUMMARY

Full stack web developer with a decade of experience in telecommunications, inventory management, quality control, and team management. Communicate effectively while leading teams and contributing to ongoing projects. Wear multiple hats to meet deadlines and achieve corporate goals.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML, CSS, Javascript

Skills: React.js, Material UI, Bulma, UIKit, Handlebars, Bootstrap, MongoDB, MySQL, Passport, Node,

JQuery, Express.js

PROJECTS

Taskably-2.0 https://github.com/toveson/taskably-2.0 | https://arcane-sands-96523.herokuapp.com/

- A program to manage products, orders, employees, and customers
- Tools used: React, Bulma, Axios, Bcrypt, JSONWebToken, Express, MySQL, MongoDB
- Developed in collaboration with a group of developers

Weather-Dashboard github.com/toveson/Weather-Dashboard/toveson.github.io/Weather-Dashboard/

- This application allows the user to search a city and receive detailed, current weather information as well as a five-day forecast.
- Tools used: Bootstrap, Jquery, moment, HTML, Javascript

Day-Planner github.com/toveson/Day-Planner | toveson.github.io/Day-Planner/

- This application gives users the ability to easily save appointments to hour time blocks.
- Tools used: Bootstrap, Font AwesomeTools, Jquery, Moment, HTML, Javascript, CSS

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Teaching Assistant, University of Utah, Salt Lake City, Utah	2021 – Current
 Assist instructor by helping students work through new material Tutor, University of Utah, Salt Lake City, Utah 	2021 – Current
 Assist students with any JavaScript questions they need help with 	
Inventory Specialist, Clear Home, Orem, Utah	2011 – Current

- 2019-Inventory Specialist
- 2018 Promoted to Regional Field Supervisor
- 2017 Moved into a corporate role assessing quality control on installations.
- 2011 Installation Technician and was promoted to a Lead technician Position in 2013

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Certification: The University of Utah, Salt Lake City, UT, January 2021